{
    "subject": "resource/Alfred_Peet",
    "predicate": "property/placeOfBirth",
    "object": "resource/Alkmaar",
    "human_readable": "Alfred Peet was born in Alkmaar.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7598491907119751,
            "question": "Where was Alfred Peet born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7112258076667786,
            "question": "In what year was Alfred Peet born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4551486372947693,
            "question": "What is Alfred Peet known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27352362871170044,
            "question": "Who were some of Alfred Peet's notable collaborators?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2324468195438385,
            "question": "How did Alfred Peet's upbringing influence his career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20436497032642365,
            "question": "What city is associated with Alfred Peet's legacy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19610929489135742,
            "question": "Is Alfred Peet considered a pioneer in the coffee industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.192821204662323,
            "question": "Did Alfred Peet have any famous business ventures?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1632828712463379,
            "question": "What type of business did Alfred Peet establish?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11071319878101349,
            "question": "What is the impact of Alfred Peet's work on modern coffee culture?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Alfred Peet was born in Alkmaar.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3474_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of business did Alfred Peet establish?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3474_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Alfred Peet have any famous business ventures?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3474_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Alfred Peet considered a pioneer in the coffee industry?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3474_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3474_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3474_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3474_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3474_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3474_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3474_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3474_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3474_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3474_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3474_75.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Alfred Peet was born in Alkmaar\" based on the provided context information:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Alfred Peet was born on March 10, 1920, in Alkmaar, Noord-Holland, Netherlands (document 1), and also mention his birthplace as Alkmaar, the Netherlands, in several other documents (documents 3, 5, and 7). Therefore, the information in the documents supports the triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Alfred Peet was born in Alkmaar, The Netherlands, which supports the statement that Alfred Peet was born in Alkmaar."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}